http://rogerschocolates.com/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Customer Service: 1-800-663-2220
Search >
(0)
Cart
(0)
Remove Item
Privacy Policy Rogers' Chocolates Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the finest quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. The Policy guides how we collect, store and use information about customers and prospects, and it will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' changing needs.
Questions and comments? Rogers' Chocolates Ltd. Privacy Policy has been developed out of respect for the privacy preferences and choices of our customers. We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your concerns.
Our Policy recognizes that Personal Data deserves protection. Personal Data includes, for example, e-mail addresses, billing information, delivery addresses, gift recipient names and addresses, and "click stream" data that tracks visitor activity on our Web site and on-line service.
OUR POLICY PROVIDES THE FOLLOWING
1. Notice. Where not clearly a part of an on-line transaction, we will inform you about why we are collecting Personal Data and how we intend to use it. For instance, we need to collect and store your name, address, and other basic Personal Data, to provide you with the product or service you requested, as well as for billing purposes. 2. Prior Approval. From time to time, we are approached by companies and organizations that have a product or service that they believe may be of interest to you. Rogers' Chocolates will never share your Personal Data with any Company, individual or organization that is not affiliated with Rogers' Chocolates without first obtaining your approval to do so.
3. Security. We will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of your Personal Data and your gift list recipients' data on our premises. 4. Review and Correction. We are continuing to enhance our procedures to enable you to review and correct, upon request, the Personal Information we collect from you. Currently, we require that you make such a request in a manner that can be verified.
The first Rogers' chocolates were made in 1885 by Charles "Candy" Rogers in the back of his grocery store in Victoria, B.C. He quickly became a popular man. In 1891, Rogers expanded his chocolate operation to the company's current heritage storefront on Government Street in Victoria and the rest, as they say, is history.
Learn More
Visit Us on Facebook
Privacy Policy
Worldwide Shipping
Careers
Terms & Conditions
Wholesale
© Copyright Rogers' Chocolates Inc. 2019 | Website design by Eclipse360
Back to top
Free Shipping in Canada on Deliveries $85+ See Details Here
